The one who tries to rule over
demons with violence and power...
The Demon King Ahriman.
His desires inspired him to try to
bring the demon world under one ruler.
But the demon king halted his invasion
because of a certain problem.
And that problem...
Demon King Ahriman's only daughter Doux...
Want some?
is too kind!
THE DEMON KING'S DAUGHTER MUST SHREWDLY
OPPRESS THE HUMANS!!
"The Demon King's Daughter Must Shrewdly
Oppress the Humans!!"
Oh?
Sariya daisies.
These will make Rashida and Khawla happy.
Like mother, like daughter.
They both love flowers.
Come on. I just picked them, too.
Looks like the mining for
magic stones is going well.
Yes, ma'am. Though some of the
riffraff give us some trouble.
You mean the demon hunter
that was just brought in?
If he gives us trouble, we might just
grill him up and eat him.
Absolutely not. Slaves provide
the vital manpower we need.
There are other ways we can use him.
Sweet potatoes! Sweet potatoes!
Lady Doux?!
Big Sister Jahi!
Wh-What brings you here?
Papa brought me some sweet potatoes!
That doting dad abandoned the
invasion for what exactly?!
But there's lots, so I wanted to eat
them with everyone including the humans
and you, Big Sister Jahi!
Come now, Doux! I explicitly told you
that you mustn't share with the slaves!
Papa!
No, really, what is this family doing?
You must be more firm, Your Majesty!
Those actions of yours are exactly what's
making Lady Doux's kindness worse!
What?! They are?!
Lady Doux, did I not tell you before?
If you remain kind, the demon king
will be too worried to do his job properly.
You must become more demon-like
and fill your heart with cruelty!
I'm sorry...
There must be something we can do...
The trial using the villagers the
other day didn't go well at all.
Fear not, Your Majesty!
I have prepared a new trial for Lady Doux.
Oho? And what kind of trial is that?
A trial where she must shrewdly oppress
a disruptive, unruly slave
by whipping him into
submission through fear and pain.
Ah, that's a brilliant idea!
But this will be a bit dangerous, so we must
prepare accordingly to
ensure Lady Doux's safety.
There's no need to worry about that.
Here you are, Doux. I came here
because I forgot to give you this.
What's this?
Now you are the rightful
wielder of that staff, Doux.
What kind of staff is it?
Just watch.
Your Majesty, what are you doing?!
Don't move.
It's just a plain ol' stick, Papa.
Lady Doux!
This allows the user of the staff
to turn anyone with malice,
murderous intent, and malevolence
into dust with just a touch.
It's my very own special staff.
This should put your mind at ease.
Now, go work hard on your trial!
Yay, sand!
So what happens when she touches a demon?
Yay!
Hmm... No idea.
You again, Demon Hunter?!
If you just followed orders
and worked, you wouldn't get hurt!
Hey, you got any loot on you?
I have nothing. Please, just let me through.
What's that?
Hey, now. Don't defy us.
Tch. Man, we've barely got anything to
eat because that Ahriman guy's army's
been forcing their way through.
Now we're stuck attacking these
broke humans out in the sticks.
There should be a small village up ahead.
We can probably find something
a bit more decent there.
There sure wasn't anything in
that house we just went to.
Rashida! Khawla!
We threw that demon hunter into the dungeons.
He refuses to do what he's told.
Ah! Big Sister!
Why do you keep moving away from me?
B-Because there'd be a lack of alertness
during your trials if you're near me.
Demons are literally made up of malice,
murderous intent, and malevolence!
MALICE
MURDEROUS INTENT
MALEVOLENCE
So of course, we're going to
turn into dust if you touch us!
More importantly, do you understand what
I meant by "must shrewdly oppress them"?
Yup!
You just need to whip and
grill them until they obey.
You understand, right?
Yup!
Does she really understand?
Well, I'll worry about that later.
The ultimate goal right now is to make Lady
Doux understand that humans are the enemy.
We're here.
I'm sure that if Lady Doux understands
that humans are ugly and dangerous creatures,
she will eventually be wary of
them and see them as enemies.
And a prisoner with a chip on his
shoulder will be perfect for that.
Now, Lady Doux, use this
whip on the prisoner and...
Wow, it's all dark!
Hey!
What's a brat like you doing here?
I'm not a brat. I'm Doux.
Perfect! She ended up meeting the
demon hunter I wanted her to see.
Where'd you get those toy horns from?
They're not toys. Demons grow horns.
Yeah, I guess you're right.
So, what are you doing here?
Did you come to kill me?
Good.
If he continues to intimidate her like that,
Lady Doux will come to hate the humans
and will be able to oppress the
humans on her own...
Nope! I came to bring you mushrooms!
You "must shrewdly oppress him!"
Not "mushrooms," Lady Doux!
And I'm supposed to grill you, too!
You've somehow turned all
of this into cooking!
Yeah, mushrooms sure are delicious.
Yup! They are!
They're great in hot pot, too.
It's almost hot pot season!
Are you looking forward to it?
Uh-huh! I am!
He's absolutely toying with her!
What are they plotting, siccing
a kid like this on me?
Hot pot! Hot pot!
I'm not going to obey you.
Huh?
If you're going to kill me,
just do it already!
There's no place for me in this world anyway!
Place?
You got any loot on you?
If you give it to us, we
won't destroy your village.
Oh, hey. It's the human we just cut down.
Did you want us to finish you off?
You stupid human!
You bastard!
What the hell's your problem?!
Who do you think you are?!
Assim.
That mark appears when one is drenched in
demon's blood. A curse that won't disappear.
The mark of a demon hunter.
Demons looking for revenge will be drawn by
your mark and will come to the village again.
I realize how awful it is of me to ask you
this when you just saved our village...
But please leave.
Ever since then,
I lost my place in this world.
Nothing anyone or anything
can do to me will scare me.
I am a demon hunter. I'll
even kill demon children—
It opened!
What?!
How did you use that staff for that?!
Didn't you hear what I just
said? I just said I'd kill you!
Yes, good. Show just how
negative humans can be.
But if you lay a single finger on
Lady Doux, you'll turn into dust.
Let's play a staring game!
No!
Doux is all alone, too.
What?
I'm all alone when Papa and
Big Sister Jahi are working.
I wait in my room reading picture
books and playing with blocks.
That's not what I'm talking—
But...
it gets lonely waiting all by myself...
So when I get really lonely, I go
outside to be with a bunch of friends.
Animals, humans, and
the older demons play with me.
And because you're here right
now, Doux isn't alone.
And Doux is here with you,
so you're not alone, either!
No, it's all right.
The moment he touches her, he'll turn to dust.
Why is he not turning to dust?!
What just...
I wanna touch your head!
You truly are an interesting little girl.
You probably don't even know what
"demon hunter" means, do you?
Nope! But you probably shouldn't
do that if you'll end up all alone.
You're right. Then maybe I'll just
go hunt down some mushrooms instead.
Doux wants to eat some!
Then I'll just have to bring you back lots.
Ah! It's Big Sister Jahi!
Lady Doux... What am I going to do with you?
Did Doux do a good job?
H-Huh? I didn't turn to dust?
It's... It's all right, Lady
Doux! You did a great job!
Really?
But make sure you don't go opening up locks
without permission from now on, all right?
Okay!
Jahi, how did things go?
I-I'd call it a huge success!
Papa! The mushrooms turned out great!
I see, I see.
Wait, where?
But why didn't I turn into dust?
THE DEMON KING'S ADVISOR TEACHES TOO WELL!!
"The Demon King's Advisor Teaches Too Well!!"
You sure are working hard
now. Did something happen?
Oh, just enjoyed some mushrooms.
Huh?
It sure is hot though.
We'll just have to deal with
that for a little longer.
Winter will be here soon.
From what I heard, it's basically
this hot here all year round.
What?!
I mean, seasonally, it's been
winter outside for a while now.
"YOU'RE A SNOWMAN"
LYRICS: KANATA NAKAMURA
COMPOSITION AND ARRANGEMENT: TAKERU TAKEMIYA
SONG: DOUX
It's starting to snow
It's coming down all fluffy
It's so strange that it keeps piling up
The ground's all white now
It's cold, but somehow so warm
Let's roll a giant snowball
It's all fluffy like yarn
Its round eyes are smiling, too
It's nice to meet you, it's nice to meet you
You're a snowman
Before you know it
You're everyone's friend
I came out here because I wanted to
give Lady Doux a trial out here but...
Big Sister Jahi, are you cold?
Are you all warm now?
This is for you, okay?
Huh?
You throw one, too!
Honestly... Just for a little bit.
I'm so sorry, Lady Doux!
I thought I held back enough!
You're amazing, Big Sister Jahi!
How did you do that? Did you use magic?
Er, no, I didn't use any magic...
Oho, attack magic training, you say?
Yes. From what I've witnessed, many demons
become more evil once they
learn how to use attack magic.
I see! If she learns attack magic, she'll
naturally become more demon-like...
The only problem is if Lady Doux can
use attack magic in the first place...
That won't be a problem.
Your Majesty, what is that?
Dark matter.
If a human touches it, they'll get sucked in,
but if a demon consumes this, it will
amplify their magic and evil nature.
He just went and created
something insane again!
Now go, Doux!
Consume this dark matter
and start your training!
Does the dark matter taste good?
It's sweet.
Lady Doux, you wanted to know how to
throw a snowball earlier, correct?
Yup.
Then let me show you how.
I actually used magic!
Or at least, I'll say that.
For example, even with this small stone,
if you use strengthening magic...
You can even throw it into the horizon.
Doux wants to do that, too!
Okay, she's very interested.
Please listen well.
Imagine water flowing from
your heart into your hand.
Yes! Now, throw!
Hiyah!
W-Well, everyone has things
they're good and bad at.
There are various kinds of magic, so
if you learn one that you excel at...
Can you do all
different kinds, Big Sister Jahi?
Huh? Yes, somewhat.
That's amazing! Doux wants to
see even more different kinds!
V-Very well, then. If you insist...
This is a fire spell called Flare.
Would you like to try it?
Yeah! Yeah!
I did it!
That's not even fire...
Let's try something else.
LIGHTNING
Look! Look!
It's a little Papa!
EARTH
Boom!
TREE
Grow big and strong, okay?
WATER
It's nice and cool!
WIND
This is far too peaceful!
She's not growing more violent at all!
She's just finding new ways to play!
Hey, does that not go out?
Huh? Oh...
Fire magic will only go out when you
use ice magic, which opposes it.
All right. That's enough for today...
I did it! I did it!
Th-That was amazing, Lady Doux!
Even I cannot produce something of that level!
Big Sister Jahi!
Yes?
I wanna do that to humans!
What did you just say?!
I wanna do that where all
the humans are working!
We've done it, Your Majesty!
Finally... Finally! Lady Doux
has awakened to her evil side!
Is that true, Jahi?
Yes! Right about now, I'm certain that
Lady Doux is tormenting the humans with ice!
I see... So Doux has finally...
This should finally set Lady Doux down
the path of becoming a demon.
Jahi, thank you for raising Doux so well.
I thank you from the bottom of my heart.
Your words honor me, Your Majesty.
How many years has it
been since I've seen snow?
It's so nice and cool!
What's that?
An ice pop! Some girl named
Doux gave it to me.
Here you go!
Lady Doux.
Papa!
This is brilliant, Doux!
How in the world did it turn out like this?!
I'm giving everyone ice pops right now.
Why would you do that?!
Why would you waste so much magic
potential on something so useless?
Because it feels nice and cool.
That's right, Jahi. It's nice and
cool now, so it's not a waste.
We should be celebrating her growth first.
Big Sister Jahi, are you still cold?
Now, you're all warm!
Papa, I'll give you a white beard!
No, don't!